

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Dedicated Virtual Assistant with a year of experience as a call center agent handling both inbound and outbound calls. A freelance software developer specialized in back-end development and competent enough in front-end development using new technologies.

EDUCATION

ACTS COMPUTER COLLEGE

Associate in Computer Science

TESDA

Basic Computer Literacy and Computer
Hardware NCII Certificate Holder

ACHIEVEMENTS

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND IT CHALLENGE (COMPIT) 2015

ACADEMIC DAY (ACAD) 2016
PROGRAMMING CONTEST

NATIONAL CERTIFICATE II IN COMPUTER
HARDWARE SERVICING

CONTACT

+639755655696
maangeloatienza@gmail.com
Blk 1 Lt 55 Aster St. San Miguel
Sto Tomas, Batangas
Linkedin
Github

EXPERIENCE

SITEL PHILIPPINES

Customer Service Sept. Representative

Sept. 2016 - February 2017

- Worked with a US based campaign which is a retail account - MACY'S
- Primary responsibility with MACY'S is to process orders and do service recovery.
- Handled COMCAST on the billing dept..
- Takes in payment or offer upgrades to the current service.

OMEGA HEALTHCARE

Billing Department/ Feb. 2017 - May 2017 Customer Service

 Takes in payment for the ambulance service received. Adding insurance information as well.



BACK-END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

Data Extraction

Data mining

Web development

Front-end and Back-end

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap

PHP

Laravel

MySQL NodeJS

ExpressJS

AngularJS

VueJS

Reactjs

Ghost CMS

Shopify API Development

Customer Service(Inbound and outbound calling)

EXPERIENCE

CHRONOS STRATEGIES

Customer Service May 2017- August 2017 Representative

- Worked for Durable Medical Equipment companies as a Customer support
- Check if the product was received and assist customer thru phone on how to wear the braces.
- Retain customerts that wants to send back the braces or cancel the order.

HOME BASED WORKS

Data entry specialist Sept 2017 - Dec 2019

- Search for properties that owner's wants to sell
- Pile information such as address and contact information.
- Make those information as leads.

CODE DISRUPTOS INC.

Software Developer March 2018 - Aug 2019

- Works as a back-end developer using NodeJS and MySQL
- Create RESTFUL APIs for e-commerce and logistic web applications



FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROJECTS

LINKS

https://ichoose.ph https://www.rakwireless.com https://luxein.com (contributed with some features)

https://news.rakwireless.com https://docs.rakwireless.com

 Some projects are use internally by clients and links cannot be posted for confidentiality

EXPERIENCE

ICHOOSEPH

Front-end Developer June 2019 - Dec 2019

• Currently working as a front-end developer for an insurance company.

RAKWIRELESS

Full-stack Developer Jan 2020 - Present

- Works for an IoT company to create the Web portal for marketing and Licensing web application for their products
- Maintains/coded the documentation site for the products
- Create internal API for features for web portal and third-party apps
- Maintains/coded the news portal for the company



INSTRUCTOR

BOOTCAMP LECTURE SCOPE

- Introduction to programming using Scratch
- Fullstack Web Development Course
 - o HTML
 - CSS
 - BOOTSTRAP
 - JAVASCRIPT
 - NODEJS
 - EXPRESSJS
 - PHP
 - LARAVEL

EXPERIENCE

CODE DISRUPTORS INC.

• Teaches kids ages 8=13 about introduction to programming using Scratch

KODEGO PH

Full-stack Developer Jan 2023 - Present Instructor

• Conducts bootcamps for full-stack web development.